{
    "subject": "resource/Peter_Higgs",
    "predicate": "ontology/award",
    "object": "resource/Nobel_Prize_in_Physics",
    "human_readable": "Peter Higgs received a Nobel Prize in Physics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9325010776519775,
            "question": "For what achievement did Peter Higgs receive a Nobel Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9073737859725952,
            "question": "Name the person who received a Nobel Prize in Physics."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8872173428535461,
            "question": "In what year did Peter Higgs receive the Nobel Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8790664672851562,
            "question": "What category did Peter Higgs win a Nobel Prize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8748653531074524,
            "question": "Who received a Nobel Prize in Physics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7748637795448303,
            "question": "Is Peter Higgs known for his work in physics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7479729652404785,
            "question": "Who is associated with a Nobel Prize in Physics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.609741747379303,
            "question": "What is the name of the award Peter Higgs won?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5369498133659363,
            "question": "What prestigious award did Peter Higgs win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2557164430618286,
            "question": "What field is the Nobel Prize related to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Peter Higgs received a Nobel Prize in Physics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8658_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What prestigious award did Peter Higgs win?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8658_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the award Peter Higgs won?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8658_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is associated with a Nobel Prize in Physics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8658_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8658_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8658_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8658_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8658_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8658_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8658_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8658_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8658_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8658_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8658_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as Peter Higgs was awarded the Nobel Prize in Physics in 2013 for his discovery of the mechanism that contributes to our understanding of the origin of mass of subatomic particles."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Peter Higgs was awarded the Nobel Prize in Physics in 2013 for his theoretical discovery of how elemental particles achieve mass. This information directly supports the query that Peter Higgs received a Nobel Prize in Physics."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}